[
    {
        "answer": "tremendously",
        "choices": [
            "appropriately",
            "uniquely",
            "tremendously",
            "decidedly"
        ],
        "question": "enormously"
    },
    {
        "answer": "stipulations",
        "choices": [
            "stipulations",
            "interrelations",
            "jurisdictions",
            "interpretations"
        ],
        "question": "provisions"
    },
    {
        "answer": "randomly",
        "choices": [
            "dangerously",
            "densely",
            "randomly",
            "linearly"
        ],
        "question": "haphazardly"
    },
    {
        "answer": "conspicuous",
        "choices": [
            "battered",
            "ancient",
            "mysterious",
            "conspicuous"
        ],
        "question": "prominent"
    },
    {
        "answer": "pinnacle",
        "choices": [
            "completion",
            "pinnacle",
            "outset",
            "decline"
        ],
        "question": "zenith"
    },
    {
        "answer": "imperfect",
        "choices": [
            "tiny",
            "imperfect",
            "lustrous",
            "crude"
        ],
        "question": "flawed"
    },
    {
        "answer": "desperately",
        "choices": [
            "typically",
            "conceivably",
            "tentatively",
            "desperately"
        ],
        "question": "urgently"
    },
    {
        "answer": "eaten",
        "choices": [
            "bred",
            "caught",
            "eaten",
            "supplied"
        ],
        "question": "consumed"
    },
    {
        "answer": "coming",
        "choices": [
            "coming",
            "arrest",
            "financing",
            "stability"
        ],
        "question": "advent"
    },
    {
        "answer": "succinctly",
        "choices": [
            "powerfully",
            "positively",
            "freely",
            "succinctly"
        ],
        "question": "concisely"
    },
    {
        "answer": "greetings",
        "choices": [
            "information",
            "ceremonies",
            "greetings",
            "privileges"
        ],
        "question": "salutes"
    },
    {
        "answer": "alone",
        "choices": [
            "alert",
            "restless",
            "alone",
            "fearless"
        ],
        "question": "solitary"
    },
    {
        "answer": "accelerate",
        "choices": [
            "permit",
            "determine",
            "accelerate",
            "accompany"
        ],
        "question": "hasten"
    },
    {
        "answer": "endurance",
        "choices": [
            "endurance",
            "skill",
            "generosity",
            "disturbance"
        ],
        "question": "perseverance"
    },
    {
        "answer": "imaginative",
        "choices": [
            "familiar",
            "imaginative",
            "apparent",
            "logical"
        ],
        "question": "fanciful"
    },
    {
        "answer": "demonstrated",
        "choices": [
            "demonstrated",
            "published",
            "repeated",
            "postponed"
        ],
        "question": "showed"
    },
    {
        "answer": "continually",
        "choices": [
            "instantly",
            "continually",
            "rapidly",
            "accidentally"
        ],
        "question": "constantly"
    },
    {
        "answer": "subjects",
        "choices": [
            "training",
            "salaries",
            "subjects",
            "benefits"
        ],
        "question": "issues"
    },
    {
        "answer": "supply",
        "choices": [
            "supply",
            "impress",
            "protect",
            "advise"
        ],
        "question": "furnish"
    },
    {
        "answer": "expensive",
        "choices": [
            "expensive",
            "beautiful",
            "popular",
            "complicated"
        ],
        "question": "costly"
    },
    {
        "answer": "acknowledged",
        "choices": [
            "successful",
            "depicted",
            "acknowledged",
            "welcomed"
        ],
        "question": "recognized"
    },
    {
        "answer": "location",
        "choices": [
            "climate",
            "latitude",
            "sea",
            "location"
        ],
        "question": "spot"
    },
    {
        "answer": "earn",
        "choices": [
            "earn",
            "print",
            "trade",
            "borrow"
        ],
        "question": "make"
    },
    {
        "answer": "frequently",
        "choices": [
            "definitely",
            "frequently",
            "chemically",
            "hardly"
        ],
        "question": "often"
    },
    {
        "answer": "relaxed",
        "choices": [
            "frontier",
            "boring",
            "farming",
            "relaxed"
        ],
        "question": "easygoing"
    },
    {
        "answer": "argument",
        "choices": [
            "war",
            "argument",
            "election",
            "competition"
        ],
        "question": "debate"
    },
    {
        "answer": "thin",
        "choices": [
            "clear",
            "freezing",
            "thin",
            "poisonous"
        ],
        "question": "narrow"
    },
    {
        "answer": "planned",
        "choices": [
            "planned",
            "explained",
            "studied",
            "discarded"
        ],
        "question": "arranged"
    },
    {
        "answer": "limitless",
        "choices": [
            "limitless",
            "relative",
            "unusual",
            "structural"
        ],
        "question": "infinite"
    },
    {
        "answer": "striking",
        "choices": [
            "striking",
            "prickly",
            "entertaining",
            "incidental"
        ],
        "question": "showy"
    },
    {
        "answer": "imposed",
        "choices": [
            "imposed",
            "believed",
            "requested",
            "correlated"
        ],
        "question": "levied"
    },
    {
        "answer": "skillfully",
        "choices": [
            "skillfully",
            "prudently",
            "occasionally",
            "humorously"
        ],
        "question": "deftly"
    },
    {
        "answer": "circulate",
        "choices": [
            "commercialize",
            "circulate",
            "research",
            "acknowledge"
        ],
        "question": "distribute"
    },
    {
        "answer": "differences",
        "choices": [
            "weights",
            "deposits",
            "wavelengths",
            "differences"
        ],
        "question": "discrepancies"
    },
    {
        "answer": "productive",
        "choices": [
            "productive",
            "serious",
            "capable",
            "promising"
        ],
        "question": "prolific"
    },
    {
        "answer": "unequaled",
        "choices": [
            "unrecognized",
            "unequaled",
            "alienated",
            "emulated"
        ],
        "question": "unmatched"
    },
    {
        "answer": "uniquely",
        "choices": [
            "partly",
            "uniquely",
            "patriotically",
            "suspiciously"
        ],
        "question": "peculiarly"
    },
    {
        "answer": "color",
        "choices": [
            "glare",
            "contrast",
            "color",
            "scent"
        ],
        "question": "hue"
    },
    {
        "answer": "rear",
        "choices": [
            "curved",
            "muscular",
            "hairy",
            "rear"
        ],
        "question": "hind"
    },
    {
        "answer": "accentuate",
        "choices": [
            "alter",
            "imitate",
            "accentuate",
            "restore"
        ],
        "question": "highlight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "hurriedly",
        "choices": [
            "hurriedly",
            "shrewdly",
            "habitually",
            "chronologically"
        ],
        "question": "hastily"
    },
    {
        "answer": "mild",
        "choices": [
            "cold",
            "mild",
            "short",
            "windy"
        ],
        "question": "temperate"
    },
    {
        "answer": "smile",
        "choices": [
            "exercise",
            "rest",
            "joke",
            "smile"
        ],
        "question": "grin"
    },
    {
        "answer": "orally",
        "choices": [
            "orally",
            "overtly",
            "fittingly",
            "verbosely"
        ],
        "question": "verbally"
    },
    {
        "answer": "doctor",
        "choices": [
            "chemist",
            "pharmacist",
            "nurse",
            "doctor"
        ],
        "question": "physician"
    },
    {
        "answer": "basically",
        "choices": [
            "possibly",
            "eagerly",
            "basically",
            "ordinarily"
        ],
        "question": "essentially"
    },
    {
        "answer": "sharp",
        "choices": [
            "useful",
            "simple",
            "famous",
            "sharp"
        ],
        "question": "keen"
    },
    {
        "answer": "positioned",
        "choices": [
            "rotating",
            "isolated",
            "emptying",
            "positioned"
        ],
        "question": "situated"
    },
    {
        "answer": "major",
        "choices": [
            "most",
            "numerous",
            "major",
            "exceptional"
        ],
        "question": "principal"
    },
    {
        "answer": "gradually",
        "choices": [
            "rarely",
            "gradually",
            "effectively",
            "continuously"
        ],
        "question": "slowly"
    },
    {
        "answer": "constructed",
        "choices": [
            "constructed",
            "proposed",
            "financed",
            "organized"
        ],
        "question": "built"
    },
    {
        "answer": "jobs",
        "choices": [
            "customers",
            "materials",
            "shops",
            "jobs"
        ],
        "question": "tasks"
    },
    {
        "answer": "improbable",
        "choices": [
            "improbable",
            "disagreeable",
            "different",
            "unpopular"
        ],
        "question": "unlikely"
    },
    {
        "answer": "apathetically",
        "choices": [
            "customarily",
            "bipartisanly",
            "apathetically",
            "unconventionally"
        ],
        "question": "halfheartedly"
    },
    {
        "answer": "chronicles",
        "choices": [
            "homes",
            "trails",
            "chronicles",
            "songs"
        ],
        "question": "annals"
    },
    {
        "answer": "furiously",
        "choices": [
            "distinctively",
            "mysteriously",
            "abruptly",
            "furiously"
        ],
        "question": "wildly"
    },
    {
        "answer": "acclaimed",
        "choices": [
            "judged",
            "acclaimed",
            "remembered",
            "addressed"
        ],
        "question": "hailed"
    },
    {
        "answer": "mastery",
        "choices": [
            "observation",
            "love",
            "awareness",
            "mastery"
        ],
        "question": "command"
    },
    {
        "answer": "devised",
        "choices": [
            "devised",
            "cleaned",
            "requested",
            "supervised"
        ],
        "question": "concocted"
    },
    {
        "answer": "potential",
        "choices": [
            "particular",
            "prudent",
            "potential",
            "prominent"
        ],
        "question": "prospective"
    },
    {
        "answer": "broadly",
        "choices": [
            "descriptively",
            "broadly",
            "controversially",
            "accurately"
        ],
        "question": "generally"
    },
    {
        "answer": "prolonged",
        "choices": [
            "prolonged",
            "refined",
            "lowered",
            "analyzed"
        ],
        "question": "sustained"
    },
    {
        "answer": "dangerous",
        "choices": [
            "binding",
            "exciting",
            "offensive",
            "dangerous"
        ],
        "question": "perilous"
    },
    {
        "answer": "peacefulness",
        "choices": [
            "peacefulness",
            "harshness",
            "weariness",
            "happiness"
        ],
        "question": "tranquillity"
    },
    {
        "answer": "disperse",
        "choices": [
            "disperse",
            "isolate",
            "disguise",
            "photograph"
        ],
        "question": "dissipate"
    },
    {
        "answer": "chiefly",
        "choices": [
            "occasionally",
            "cautiously",
            "consistently",
            "chiefly"
        ],
        "question": "primarily"
    },
    {
        "answer": "conversational",
        "choices": [
            "recorded",
            "misunderstood",
            "incorrect",
            "conversational"
        ],
        "question": "colloquial"
    },
    {
        "answer": "settled",
        "choices": [
            "publicized",
            "forgotten",
            "settled",
            "examined"
        ],
        "question": "resolved"
    },
    {
        "answer": "possible",
        "choices": [
            "permitted",
            "possible",
            "equitable",
            "evident"
        ],
        "question": "feasible"
    },
    {
        "answer": "rapidly",
        "choices": [
            "frequently",
            "actually",
            "rapidly",
            "repeatedly"
        ],
        "question": "expeditiously"
    },
    {
        "answer": "proportion",
        "choices": [
            "volume",
            "sample",
            "proportion",
            "profit"
        ],
        "question": "percentage"
    },
    {
        "answer": "ended",
        "choices": [
            "ended",
            "posed",
            "postponed",
            "evaluated"
        ],
        "question": "terminated"
    },
    {
        "answer": "alike",
        "choices": [
            "hard",
            "complex",
            "alike",
            "sharp"
        ],
        "question": "uniform"
    },
    {
        "answer": "solve",
        "choices": [
            "list",
            "solve",
            "divide",
            "express"
        ],
        "question": "figure"
    },
    {
        "answer": "enough",
        "choices": [
            "recent",
            "physiological",
            "enough",
            "valuable"
        ],
        "question": "sufficient"
    },
    {
        "answer": "manner",
        "choices": [
            "ration",
            "fathom",
            "craze",
            "manner"
        ],
        "question": "fashion"
    },
    {
        "answer": "sold",
        "choices": [
            "frozen",
            "sold",
            "sweetened",
            "diluted"
        ],
        "question": "marketed"
    },
    {
        "answer": "larger",
        "choices": [
            "steadier",
            "closer",
            "larger",
            "better"
        ],
        "question": "bigger"
    },
    {
        "answer": "origins",
        "choices": [
            "origins",
            "rituals",
            "cure",
            "function"
        ],
        "question": "roots"
    },
    {
        "answer": "ordinarily",
        "choices": [
            "haltingly",
            "ordinarily",
            "permanently",
            "periodically"
        ],
        "question": "normally"
    }
]